A Guide to the Arthur M. Squires Papers, 1888-1987 (Bulk 1940-1986)
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- C Series, Correspondence Files, 1947-1987, n.d.
  - Box C-9, 1958-1987, n.d. (Box 45)
    - Department of Energy (U. S.), Office of Energy Research, 1978-1985.
    - Department of Energy (U. S.), Basic Energy Sciences, 1978-1981.
    - Department of Energy (U. S.), Fossil University Programs, 1979-1982.
    - Department of Energy (U. S.), Combustion, 1979-1982.
    - Department of Energy (U. S.), General Information, 1977-1979.
    - Department of Health, Education & Welfare (U. S.), AMS' Federal Employment Forms, 1966-1969.
    - Deutch, Michael, 1970.
    - Diesel Gas, Planning Stage, 1986-1987.
    - Diesel Gas, Planning Stage, 1986, n.d.
    - Dobner, Samuel I., Research Proposal/Study, 1972, n.d.
    - Dow Chemical, 1974-1983.
    - Dorr-Oliver, 1972-1986.
    - Dorr-Oliver, 1962-1984.
    - Ducon Company, Inc., 1962-1964.
    - DuPont, 1969-1986.
    - Eastman Kodak, 1973-1974.
    - Economists, 1973-1974.
    - Edmonds, Rod, 1960-1961.
    - Edmondson, P. D., 1960-1971.
    - Elliott, D. E., 1971-1977.
  - Box C-10, 1968-1986, n.d. (Box 46)
    - Elliott, D. E., 1972-1976.
    - Elliott, D. E., 1974-1975.
    - Employment, 1971-1973.
    - Energy Systems & Policy, 1973-1985.
    - Engineering Foundation, 1980-1984.
    - Engineering Foundation, 1976-1983.
    - Engineering Foundation, Copenhagen, 1986.
    - ngineering Fundamentals, 1977.
    - England Correspondence, 1975-1986.
    - Environmental Testing Services, 1980-1981.
    - Environmental Action Groups, 1971-1982.
    - Environmental Action Groups, 1968-1970.
    - Enviro-Systems & Research, Inc., Roanoke, VA, 1976-1985.
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1970-1979.
    - EPA: Rules, 1971-1973.
    - EPA: Solid Waste, 1971-1972.
    - EPA: Standards, n.d.
    - Electric Power Research Institute (EPRI), 1967-1987.
    - EPRI, 1973-1977.
    - EPRI, 1974-1985.
    - EPRI, 1974-1977.
    - EPRI Contract, 1981-1983.
    - EPRI, San Francisco Conference, 1985.
  - Box C-11, 1951-1987. (Box 47)
    - EPRI, San Francisco Conference, 1985.
    - Energy Research & Development Administration (ERDA), Contracts, 1976-1977.
    - ERDA, 1976.
    - ERDA, 1975-1978.
    - ERDA, University Programs, 1977-1978.
    - Ernst & Ernst, 1976.
    - Essenhigh, 1967-1972.
    - Exxon, 1977-1984.
    - Exxon, 1978-1986.
    - Exxon, 1971-1984.
    - Exxon, 1958-1981.
    - Exxon, Chemically Active Fluid Bed Program, 1968-1977.
    - Exxon Grant, 1980-1981.
    - Extension Division (VPI&SU), 1977.
    - Faber, Alex W. (CPA), 1961-1985.
    - Fanning, F. H., 1959-1961.
    - Federal Energy Administration, 1976-1977.
    - Filter Promotion, 1976-1981.
    - Filter Promotion, 1967-1981.
    - Filter Promotion, 1971-1987.
  - Box C-12, 1959-1986, n.d. (Box 48)
    - Fives-Cail Babcock, 1969-1986.
    - Flame Research Committee, 1976.
    - Fluidyne, 1973, 1976.
    - FluidFire, 1965-1977.
    - FluidFire, 1977-1979.
    - Fluidization Research, Fischer-Tropsch, 1981-1985.
    - Fluidization Research, Heat Recovery, 1983-1984.
    - Fluidization Research, Heat Recovery, 1982-1983.
    - Fluor Corporation, 1970-1974.
    - FMC Corporation, 1968-1975.
    - Ford Foundation, 1971.
    - Foster-Pegg, Dynetic Systems, Inc., 1970-1971.
    - Fossil Energy Research Working Group, 1978-1979.
    - Fossil Energy Research Working Group, 1978, n.d.
    - Foster Wheeler Energy Corporation, 1961-1979.
    - Fougner, Sven, 1970.
    - Fraas, Arthur, 1974-1980.
    - Franklin Institute, 1969-1974.
    - Freeport Sulphur, 1968-1969.
    - F-T Synthesis Proposals, 1985-1986.
    - F-T Synthesis Proposals, 1985.
    - Gadelius, 1977-1981.
    - Garbo, P. W., 1960-1982.
    - Garrett Research, 1970-1973.
    - Geldart, Derek, 1968-1987.
    - Geological Survey (U. S.), 1985.
    - General Electric, 1959-1985.
    - General Telephone, 1973.
    - Germany, Business Cards, n.d.
    - Gilbert Associates, 1973.
    - Godel, A. A., 1965-1977.
    - Godel, A. A., 1969-1976.
  - Box C-13, 1947-1987. (Box 49)
    - Gordon Conference, Coal Science, 1963-1976.
    - Gordon Conference, Coal Science, 1963-1971.
    - Gotaverken Energy Systems, 1975-1986.
    - Gotaverken Energy Systems, 1975, 1986.
    - Gotaverken Energy Systems, Slides, 1985.
    - Graduate Studies (General), 1983-1987.
    - Graff, R. A., 1970-1982.
    - Graton, L. C., 1947.
    - Gulf Oil Corporation, 1967.
    - Guyana, 1980.
    - Habicht, E. R. (Hasty), Environmental Defense Fund, 1974-1982.
    - Habicht, E. R. (Hasty), Environmental Defense Fund, 1975-1982.
    - Habicht, E. R. (Hasty), Environmental Defense Fund, 1974-1977.
    - Hamielec, 1967.
    - Hamworthy Engineering, Ltd., 1981.
    - Harboe, Henrik, 1973-1986.
    - Hartley, Sir Harold, 1958-1985.
    - Hartley, Sir Harold, 1930-1972.
    - Harvard, 1960-1977.
    - Hedden, Kurt, 1972-1977.
    - Henlein, Lore, "Tender Ship" - Pre-Publication, 1983-1986.
    - Henlein, Lore, "Tender Ship" - Pre-Publication, 1982-1987.
    - Henlein, Lore, Birkhauser Correspondence, 1985-1986.
  - Box C-14, 1946-1986, n.d. (Box 50)
    - Heurtey, 1972-1977.
    - Hibbard, Walter, 1976-1986.
    - Hirt, Doug, 1983.
    - Holland Correspondence, 1977-1981.
    - Hombach, H. P., 1980.
    - Honorifics Committee, 1985.
    - Honors Colloquium, 1980.
    - Honors Colloquium, 1980.
    - Honors Colloquium, 1981.
    - Honors Colloquium, Winter 1982.
    - Honors Colloquium, Winter 1983.
    - Honors Colloquium, Fall 1984.
    - Honors Colloquium, Winter 1986.
    - Horsfall, D. W., 1972, n.d.
    - Houston University, 1974-1980.
    - Hydrocarbon Research, Inc. (HRI), Technical Data, 1953, 1959.
    - HRI, Technical Data: Index - C-SLAG-24.2, June 1949.
    - HRI, Technical Data: D-A-1-24.0 - E9.510, October 1947.
    - HRI, Technical Data: E10.100 - E22.123, 1946.
    - HRI, Technical Data: F1.240 - G16.510-5, 1952.
    - HRI, 1967-1979.
    - HRI, 1956-1979.
  - Box C-15, 1955-1985, n.d. (Box 51)
    - HRI, 1955-1978.
    - HRI, Fast Fluid Bed Annual Report (#15), 1977.
    - HRI, H-Coal Gasoline Report, 1978.
    - HRI, 1973-1976.
    - Huang, Hao-Hsin, 1982.
    - Hubbell, Cohen, Stiefel and Gross, 1980-1984.
    - Hutchison, W. K., 1960-1962.
    - IIASA, (International Institute for Applied Systems Analysis) Schloss Laxenburg, Austria, 1977-1979.
    - IIASA, 1976-1977.
    - Illinois State Geological Survey, 1972-1981.
    - India, 1971-1981.
    - India, 1977-1982.
    - India, 1981-1985.
    - India, 1978-1981.
    - India, 1977-1981.
    - India, 1978-1984.
    - Institute of Gas Technology, 1959-1983.
    - Institute of Fuel, 1973-1979.
    - Institute of Paper Chemistry, 1973.
    - Institution of Chemical Engineers (U. K.), 1960.
    - Iowa State University, 1967.
    - Ireland, 1978.
    - Isaacs, L. L., n.d.
  - Box C-16, 1959-1986, n.d. (Box 52)
    - Israel, 1971-1984.
    - Israel, 1974-1984.
    - Jaasma, Dennis, 1982-1986.
    - Japan, 1974-1983.
    - Japan, 1977-1986.
    - Johns Hopkins, 1983-1984.
    - Johns Mansville, 1973.
    - Johnson, Clarence, 1983.
    - Jones, Stacy V., 1969-1974.
    - Jones and Laughlin Steel Corporation, 1959-1978.
    - Kane, Daniel H., 1965-1985.
    - Kane, Daniel H., 1959-1964.
    - Kane, Daniel H., 1960-1962.
    - Kansas State University, Fan, 1961-1983.
    - Kapo, George, 1971-1973.
    - Katz, Stanley, 1960-1972.
    - Katz, Stanley, 1960-1980.
    - Kellogg, M. W., 1973-1986.
    - Kennecott Copper, 1970, n.d.
    - Kentucky, 1970, 1983.
    - Kirov, N. Y., 1975-1976.
    - Kolodney, Morris, 1986.
    - Koppers Company, Inc., 1957-1978.
    - KVB, Inc., 1972-1978.
    - KVB, Inc., 1973-1978.
    - Laboratory of Coal Science, n.d.
  - Box C-17, 1968-1986, n.d. (Box 53)
    - Laboratory of Coal Science, 1977-1980.
    - Laboratory of Coal Science, 1977-1979.
    - Laboratory of Coal Science, 1976-1977.
    - Laboratory of Coal Science, 1978-1979, n.d.
    - Laboratory of Coal Science, Publications, 1976-1986.
    - Laboratory of Coal Science, Progress Reports, 1977-1979.
    - Laboratory of Coal Science, Progress Reports, 1978-1979.
    - Laboratory of Coal Science, Progress Reports, 1977-1980.
    - Laboratory of Coal Science, Proposals, 1979-1980.
    - Laboratory of Coal Science, Proposals, 1977-1980.
    - LaCava, Alberto I. (CCNY), 1978-1981.
    - Landau, Ralph, 1978-1986.
    - Large, Jean-Francois (Compiegne), 1981-1984.
    - Laurendeau, N. M., n.d.
    - Library Futures, 1984-1985.
    - Lieberman, Joseph, 1968-1969.
    - Limestone Symposium, 1968.
    - Liu, Tian-xiong, 1978-1981.
    - Liu, Y. A., 1980-1981.
    - Liss, Barry, 1980-1982.
  - Box C-18, 1959-1987. (Box 54)
    - Liverpool, University of, 1960.
    - Lobo, Walter, 1985-1986.
    - Locke, Brian, National Research Development Corporation (NRDC), 1971-1977.
    - Locke, Brian, NRDC, 1959-1987.
    - LORENDAS, Long-Range Energy Supplies, 1979-1980.
    - Loven, Carl F. C., 1960.
    - Lovins, A. B., 1976-1977.
    - Lukens Steel Co., 1960.
    - LURGI, 1972-1983.
    - LURGI, 1967-1976.
    - LURGI, 1975-1980.
    - LURGI, 1972-1980.
    - LURGI, 1949-1979.
    - Lummus Company, 1961-1976.
    - Lummus Company, 1961.
    - Manuscripts in Progress, 1976-1978.
    - Manuscripts in Progress, 1979-1983.
    - Marin, William P., 1961-1971.
    - Massimilla, Leopoldo, 1962-1986.
    - McCrone, Walter C., 1962-1986.
    - McGee, Dean A., 1976-1977.
    - McGill University (Quebec), 1970, 1978.
    - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1967-1969.
    - McKee (Engineers & Constructors), 1974.
    - Metcalf, Chris, 1977-1978.
    - Micro-Reactor (Vibrated Bed), Proposal Preparation Stage of Work, 1985-1986.
  - Box C-19, 1959-1985, n.d. (Box 55)
    - Midrex, 1980.
    - Mills, Alec, 1971-1984.
    - Mining and Minerals Resources Research Institute, 1978-1985.
    - Miscellaneous, A-B.
    - Miscellaneous, C.
    - Miscellaneous, D-G.
    - Miscellaneous, H-J.
    - Miscellaneous, K-N.
    - Miscellaneous, O-S.
    - Miscellaneous, T-Z.
    - MIT (Massachusetts Institute of Technology), 1959-1984.
    - MITRE Corporation, 1977-1985.
    - Mitsubishi, 1972, 1974.
    - Mobil, 1967-1987.
    - Mobil: Grant, 1980-1982.
    - Mobil: Publications, 1975-1980, n.d.
    - Mobil: Publications, n.d.
    - Monsanto, 1959-1978.
    - Montana, 1976-1977.
    - Mosch, Steve, 1978.
    - Mt. Sinai Hospital, 1968.
    - Mustad (Norway), 1979, n.d.
    - NAPCA (National Air Pollution Control Administration), 1970.
    - NAPCA, 1967-1975.
  - Box C-20, 1959-1986. (Box 56)
    - NAPCA, 1967-1973.
    - NAPCA, 1967-1970.
    - NAPCA: Washington, 1969-1975.
    - NAPCA: Consulting, 1968-1973.
    - National Academy of Engineering, 1977-1983.
    - National Academies; National Research Council, 1977-1981.
    - National Academy of Science, Energy Study, 1972.
    - National Academy of Science, Energy Study, 1972.
    - National Research Council, Committee on Chemical Sciences, 1978-1979.
    - National Research Council, Committee on Chemical Sciences, 1977-1978.
    - National Bureau of Standards, 1970-1986.
    - National Bureau of Standards, 1978-1982.
    - National Bureau of Standards, 1959-1981.
    - National Coal Association, 1968, 1980.
    - National Coal Board, 1959-1986.
    - National Coal Board, 1960-1979.
    - National Coal Board, Test of Panel Bed Filter, 1978-1980.
  - Box C-21, 1960-1983, n.d. (Box 57)
    - National Science Foundation, 1970-1983.
    - National Science Foundation, 1972-1973.
    - National Science Foundation, 1970-1985.
    - National Science Foundation, RANN Grant on Coal Gasification to CCNY, 1971-1976.
    - National Science Foundation, RANN Grant on Coal Gasification to CCNY, 1973-1974.
    - National Science Foundation, RANN Grant on Coal Gasification to CCNY, 1973-1974.
    - "Nature" Magazine, 1981.
    - Neavel, Richard, C., 1975, n.d.
    - Newcastle University, Harry Marsh, Mesophase, Steve Ragan, Isao Mochida, 1973-1985.
    - Newcastle University, 1973-1980.
    - Newcastle University, 1977-1981.
    - Newcastle University, 1960-1983.
    - New Jersey Public Service, 1979.
    - New York State Energy Research & Development Authority, 1973-1977.
    - New York State Science Foundation, 1968-1973.
    - New York University, 1986-1987.
    - New Zealand, 1974-1978.
    - New Zealand, 1974-1975.
    - New Zealand, 1973-1984.
    - Nigeria, 1986.
    - North Dakota University, n.d.
    - Nuwco, Inc., Gene Sutherland, 1978.
    - NYC (New York City) Council on the Environment, 1973-1976.
    - NYC Council on the Environment, 1970-1974.
  - Box C-22, 1961-1986, n.d. (Box 58)
    - NYC Government, 1968-1986.
    - NY Times and Other Media, 1963-1986.
    - Oak Ridge National Laboratory (ORNL), 1979-1985.
    - ORNL, 1976-1982.
    - ORNL, 1981.
    - ORNL, 1967-1976.
    - ORNL, 1967-1978.
    - ORNL, 1976.
    - Occidental Research Corporation, 1970-1981.
    - Office of Coal Research, 1965-1978.
    - Office of Coal Research, 1965-1974.
    - Office of Coal Research, 1972-1974.
    - Office of Coal Research, 1967-1976.
    - Office of Coal Research, 1967-1976.
    - Office of Coal Research, 1971-1974.
    - Office of Science and Technology, 1968-1972.
    - Office of Technology Assessment, 1974, 1977, n.d.
    - Ontario Research Foundation, 1968-1969.
    - Oregon State University, 1975-1983.
    - Oxygen Process Promotion, 1967-1968.
    - Pall Corporation, 1961-1969.
    - Parsonnet, Victor (M. D.), 1975.
    - Patent Matters, VPI&SU, 1977-1987.
    - Patent Disclosures, 1980-1982.
    - Patent Disclosures, 1980-1982.
  - Box C-23. (Box 59)
    - 13 Patent Office Applications.
    - 1 "Letters Patent" for Japanese Patent.
  - Box C-24. (Box 60)
    - 1 Patent Office Application.
    - 3 Folders Patent Correspondence.
  - Box C-25, 1957-1987. (Box 61)
    - Peabody Coal, 1970.
    - Penner, Sol, 1978-1979.
    - Pennsylvania State University, 1967-1983.
    - Pennsylvania State University, 1967-1975.
    - Pennsylvania, University of, 1971-1976.
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1981.
    - Philadelphia and Reading, 1957-1960.
    - Phillips Petroleum Company, 1962.
    - Pittsburgh Plate Glass (PPG) Industries, Inc., 1962-1973.
    - PPG Industries, Inc., 1962-1966.
    - PPG Industries, Inc., 1959-1965.
    - Pittsburgh, University of, 1960-1985.
    - Plunkett, Jerry, 1973-1983.
    - Plunkett, Jerry, 1972-1973.
    - Poland, 1978-1986.
    - Pope, Evans and Robins, 1968-1972.
    - Pope, Evans and Robins, 1968-1973.
    - Portugal, 1977.
    - Power Cycle Promotion, 1967-1969.
    - Princeton University, 1959-1987.
    - Proctor and Gamble, 1968-1986.
    - Pro Musica (Historic), 1952-1965.
    - Pro Musica (Historic), 1953-1966.
  - Box C-26, 1959-1987, n.d. (Box 62)
    - Proposals, 1981-1987.
    - Proposals, 1977-1983.
    - Proposals, 1978-1980.
    - Proposals, 1974.
    - Proposals, 1978.
    - Prufcomp, 1983-1987.
    - Public Health Service, 1967-1970.
    - Public Service Commission, 1972-1976.
    - Purdue University, 1976.
    - Rand Corporation, 1981.
    - Rees, Mina, 1986.
    - Reh, Lothar (Also See "LURGI"), 1971-1987.
    - Rennsaelaer Polytechnic Institute, 1975-1987.
    - Research Corporation, 1976-1977.
    - Research-Cottrell, 1976-1977.
    - Research Division, VPI&SU, 1977-1982.
    - Research Triangle Institute, 1975-1976.
    - Resources for the Future, Inc., 1971.
    - Resume, 1977-1981.
    - Resume, 1978-1987.
    - Rheinbraun, 1978-1987.
    - Roberts, W. (Also See "Constructors John Brown"), 1959.
    - Rodon, Ignacio, 1976-1981.
    - Rowe, Peter, 1959-1987.
    - Saffitz, A. A., 1968-1980.
    - Safety Office, VPI&SU, 1977.
    - Saint (St.) Joe Minerals, 1976-1977.
    - Salzenstein, Marvin, 1967-1978.
    - Sancier, K. M., 1962-1981.
    - Sandia National Laboratories, 1983.
    - Schuman, S. C., 1970, n.d.
  - Box C-27, 1959-1987, n.d. (Box 63)
    - Schuman, S. C., 1968-1971.
    - Schuman, S. C., 1960-1970.
    - Science Studies Center, 1980-1987.
    - "Scientific American" Magazine, 1972-1980.
    - Scientific Design, 1979.
    - Sebba, Felix, 1975-1986.
    - Secord, Cam, 1959-1985.
    - Sheffield, University of, 1967.
    - Shinnar, Reuel, 1974-1984.
    - Shinnar, Reuel, 1979, n.d.
    - Singer, S. Fred, 1970, 1972.
    - Singmaster and Breyer, n.d.
    - Slack, A. V., 1970, 1972.
    - Slick Industries, 1969.
    - South Africa, 1971-1980.
    - South Africa, 1971-1984.
    - South Africa, 1972-1978.
    - Southern California Edison Company, 1962-1975.
    - Spaite, Paul, 1967-1986.
    - Speaking Engagements, 1974-1987.
    - Speaking Engagements, 1976-1987.
    - Speaking Engagements, 1975-1983.
    - Speaking Engagements, 1974-1976.
  - Box C-28, 1959-1985, n.d. (Box 64)
    - Speaking Engagements, 1976-1977.
    - Speaking Engagements, 1971-1972.
    - Speaking Engagements, 1971-1980.
    - Speaking Engagements, 1970-1985.
    - Speaking Engagements, 1973-1979.
    - Sporn, Phil, 1977.
    - SRI Corporation, Baltimore, 1967-1969.
    - Stal-Laval, 1973-1985.
    - Stanford Research Institute, 1959-1978.
    - Stanford University, 1978.
    - State (of VA) Air Pollution Control Board, 1983.
    - Staub, Fred, 1982.
    - Stauffer Chemical Company, 1962-1966.
    - Steel Company of Wales, 1960-1961.
    - Sternberg, H. W., 1976-1978.
    - Stern, A. C., 1970-1981.
    - Stevens Institute of Technology, 1970.
    - Stone and Webster, 1959-1962.
    - Stott, J. B., 1978-1979.
    - Studebaker-Worthington, 1971-1972.
    - Student Papers, 1976-1977.
    - Student Research, 1971-1986.
    - Students (Prospective), 1976-1977.
    - Students, 1976-1987.
    - Students, 1975-1986.
    - Sugarman, Neal, n.d.
    - Sumitomo Shoji America, Inc., 1969-1980.
    - State University of New York (SUNY) at Buffalo, 1970-1981.
  - Box C-29, 1959-1987. (Box 65)
    - Sweden, 1960-1984.
    - Sweden, 1974-1980.
    - Sweden, 1960-1974.
    - Sweden, 1973-1981.
    - Synthetic Gas Promotion, 1967-1968.
    - Ta'eed, Olinga, 1986.
    - Taplin, F. E., 1959-1961.
    - Tata Industries, 1967-1969.
    - Tau Beta Pi, 1969.
    - Technical Audit Associates, Inc., 1978.
    - Technology Review, 1971-1986.
    - Technical Societies, 1961-1967.
    - "Tender Ship": Early Draft, 1982.
    - "Tender Ship": Permissions, 1985.
    - "Tender Ship": Promotion, 1985-1986.
    - "Tender Ship": Reviews and Appreciations, 1984-1987.
    - "Tender Ship" MS Drafts.
    - "Tender Ship" MS Drafts.
    - "Tender Ship" MS Drafts.
    - "Tender Ship" MS Drafts.
    - "Tender Ship" MS Drafts.
    - "Tender Ship" MS Draft, September 1984.
    - "Tender Ship" MS Draft, September 1984.
    - "Tender Ship" MS Draft, January 1985.
  - Box C-30, 1959-1986, n.d. (Box 66)
    - Tennessee Eastman, 1975.
    - Tennessee, Univ. of, 1971-1978.
    - Texaco, 1960-1986.
    - Texas A & M, 1976.
    - Texas Tech University, 1973.
    - Tigerschiold, M., 1960.
    - Tolltreck, Ltd., 1975.
    - Tolltreck, Ltd., 1982.
    - Travel Documents, 1968-1977.
    - Trondheim, Norway, Panel Bed Filter Development, 1978-1985.
    - Trondheim, Norway, Panel Bed Filter Development, 1978-1986.
    - Trondheim, Norway, Panel Bed Filter Development, 1979-1982.
    - Trondheim, Norway, Technological University and SINTEF, 1976-1982.
    - TRW: Research Triangle Park, 1976.
    - Tullock, Gordon, 1977-1986.
    - TUNS (Technical University of Nova Scotia), 1984-1986.
    - Turkey, 1977-1979.
    - TVA (Tennessee Valley Authority), 1970-1976.
    - Union Carbide, 1962-1985.
    - Union Carbide, 1965-1982.
    - Union Electric Company, 1959-1961.
    - United Aircraft, 1969-1971.
    - United Coal (Bristol, VA), 1980-1986.
    - United Coke and Chemicals, Ltd., 1960-1964.
    - United Nations, 1965-1971.
    - United Steel Companies, Ltd. (Rotherham), 1960.
    - VPI&SU UDP (University Distinguished Professor), 1981-1987.
    - VPI&SU UDP, 1981-1984.
    - VPI&SU UDP, 1978-1985.
    - UOP (Universal Oil Products), 1970-1976.
    - U. S. A., Business Cards, n.d.
    - U. S. Army, 1962-1975.
    - U. S. Information Agency, 1973-1974.
    - U. S. Steel, 1959-1971.
  - Box C-31, 1959-1984, n.d. (Box 67)
    - U. S. S. R., 1976.
    - U. S. S. R., 1975-1977.
    - Utah, University of, 1959-1980.
    - Vanderbilt University, 1982.
    - Venezuela, Business Cards, n.d.
    - Vielstich, W., 1976.
    - VPI&SU, 1974-1976.
    - VPI&SU, 1976-1984.
    - VPI&SU, 1976-1978.
    - VPI&SU, 1973-1978.
    - VPI&SU Alumni, 1980.
    - VA Center for Coal and Energy Research (VACCER), 1978-1980.
    - VACCER, 1978-1980.
    - VACCER, 1977-1980.
    - VACCER, 1977-1985.
    - VACCER, 1978-1986.
    - VACCER, 1983-1986.
    - VA Military Institute, 1982.
    - VA State Government, 1976-1981.
    - Visitors, 1970.
    - Voice, E. W., 1958-1960.
    - Volk, William, 1977-1979.
    - Wales Gas Board, 1959-1960.
    - Wang, Charles P. (Aerospace Corporation), 1980.
    - Warner-Lambert, 1966-1967.
    - Waters, P. L., 1970-1974.
    - Wender, Irving J., 1979-1982.
  - Box C-32, 1959-1987, n.d. (Box 68)
    - Westinghouse, 1967-1987.
    - Wentworth Brothers, Inc., 1977.
    - Whessoe Project Engineers, 1970.
    - West Virginia University, 1970-1981.
    - West Virginia University, 1968-1982.
    - West Virginia Company, 1980.
    - Whitmire, David, 1978-1982.
    - Wightman, J. P., 1981-1982.
    - Wightman, J. P., 1981-1982.
    - Williams, C. W., 1960-1962.
    - Wills, George, 1980-1981.
    - Wingaersheek, 1965-1976.
    - Wisconsin, University of, 1980.
    - Wyoming, University of, 1971.
    - Wynne, David, n.d.
    - Wynne-Jones, 1959-1960.
    - Woodall-Duckham, 1977-1979.
    - Yang, J. C., 1982-1986.
    - Yerushalmi, Joseph, 1972-1986.
    - Yerushalmi, Joseph, 1972-1981.
    - Yerushalmi, Joseph, 1974.
    - Yugoslavia, 1975-1982.
    - Zenz, F. A., 1959-1982.
    - Zenz, F. A., 1959-1966.
    - 5 Audio Tapes of AMS' Speaking Engagements.
    - Assorted Unlabeled Negatives.
- D Series, Diaries, 1951-1982.
  - Box D-1, 1968-1982. (Box 69)
    - Trip Diary, 7/12/68-2/8/69.
    - Trip Diary, 2/8/69-7/27/70.
    - Trip Diary, 7/27/70-12/8/70.
    - Trip Diary, 10/26/70-5/21/71.
    - Trip Diary, 6/10/71-4/19/72.
    - Trip Diary, 4/19/72-8/28/73.
    - Trip Diary, 8/28/73-4/10/74.
    - Trip Diary, 4/10/74-1/9/75.
    - Trip Diary, 1/12/75-8/25/75.
    - Trip Diary, 1/19/76-6/28/76.
    - Trip Diary, 6/28/76-4/15/77.
    - Trip Diary, 5/9/77-11/9/77.
    - Trip Diary, 12/1/77-7/17/78.
    - Trip Diary, 7/17/78-7/14/79.
    - Trip Diary, 7/13/79-7/1/80.
    - Trip Diary, 7/1/80-1/17/81.
    - Trip Diary, 2/5/81-11/4/82.
  - Box D-2, 1951-1963. (Box 70)
    - Daily Diary, 6/9/51-5/2/52.
    - Daily Diary, 11/12/52-4/7/54.
    - Daily Diary, 12/13/54-12/7/55.
    - Daily Diary, 6/20/55-10/7/55.
    - Daily Diary, 1/2/56-10/19/56.
    - Daily Diary, 10/24/56-4/3/57.
    - Daily Diary, 4/5/57-12/9/57.
    - Daily Diary, 1/7/58-10/15/58.
    - Daily Diary, 10/19/58-2/19/59.
    - Daily Diary, 2/26/59-4/12/59.
    - Daily Diary, 6/8/59-9/29/59.
    - Calculations, 7/4/59-11/25/59.
    - Daily Diary, 9/29/59-3/10/60.
    - Daily Diary, 3/14/60-4/13/60.
    - Daily Diary, 2/29/60-10/27/60.
    - Daily Diary, 7/22/60-9/23/60.
    - Daily Diary, 9/23/60-12/18/60.
    - Daily Diary, 12/18/60-1/8/61.
    - Daily Diary, 1/8/61-1/28/61.
    - Daily Diary, n.d.
    - Daily Diary, 1/8/61-1/28/61.
    - Daily Diary, 1/28/61-2/16/61.
    - Daily Diary, 2/16/61-3/6/61.
    - Daily Diary, 3/6/61-3/24/61.
    - Daily Diary, 3/24/61-4/30/61.
    - Daily Diary, 5/1/61-9/24/61.
    - Daily Diary, 9/24/61-1/7/61.
    - Daily Diary, 1/7/62-2/2/62.
    - Daily Diary, 2/2/62-2/25/62.
    - Daily Diary, 2/25/62-4/1/62.
    - Daily Diary, 4/1/62-4/20/62.
    - Daily Diary, 4/20/62-6/10/62.
    - Daily Diary, 6/10/62-8/29/62.
    - Daily Diary, 8/29/62-11/1/62.
    - Daily Diary, 11/1/62-12/4/62.